

# **Quentin Dangles**UX/UI DESIGNER

# PROFILE

Throughout my 7 years working side-by-side with clients, patients and customers, I've developed strong empathy and communication skills. UX/UI design is a perfect game field to continue applying my professional and soft skills for the betterment of humanity.

### CONTACT

- qyu.dangles@gmail.com
- +33 6-12-85-44-70
- in /quentin-dangles

# **EDUCATION**

IronHack
UX/UI designer certificate 2019

Institut Dauphine d'osteopathie Osteopathy Diploma 2013

High School Marie Curie Scientific Baccalaureate, 2006

### TOOLS

Sketch, Flinto, Photoshop, Trello, Marvel, Invision

# SKILLS

- Trilingual French, English and Japanese with great communication skills.
- Successful working in a team environment, as well as autonomously.
- High adaptability and ability to multi-task.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# Skye Niseko (5-stars Hotel), Duty Manager.

JAN 2019 - MAY 2019.

(HOKKAIDO, JAPAN)

- Handled planning and managed a team of 20 people of different backgrounds and nationalities.
- Raised customer satisfaction by 20% in 6 months.

# **NES Global School**, Foreign Language instructor

APR 2017 - JAN 2019

(TOKYO, JAPAN)

- Collaborated with teaching staff and administrators to foster a positive student experience.
- Identified students with special requirements and created individualized plans.

# Louis Vuitton, Assistant manager Headquarter

FEB 2016 - DEC 2016

(PARIS, FRANCE)

- Developed strong communication and organizational skills.
- Worked efficiently under pressure with very demanding visitors.

### Osteopath

DEC 2013 - DEC 2016

(PARIS, FRANCE)

- Developed strong empathy and human relationship skills.
- Identified patients' care requirements, focused on their needs and acted on them.